<rss xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" version="2.0"><channel><title>ZiXuan｜子轩</title><link>http://example.org/</link><description>This is My New Hugo Site</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en</language><managingEditor>zixuanzhang.x@gmail.com (Zixuan Zhang)</managingEditor><webMaster>zixuanzhang.x@gmail.com (Zixuan Zhang)</webMaster><lastBuildDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 13:53:54 -0400</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Rust Resources</title><link>http://example.org/posts/rust-resources/</link><pubDate>Thu, 16 Jun 2022 13:53:54 -0400</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/rust-resources/</guid><description><![CDATA[Books Getting Started The Rust Programming Language: everything you need to get started with Rust Rust By Example: a collection of runnable examples that illustrate various Rust concepts and standard libraries Intermediate The Cargo Book: Rust package manager Asynchronous Programming in Rust: a comprehensive, up-to-date guide to using Rust&rsquo;s async language features and libraries Rust API Guidelines:a set of recommendations on how to design and present APIs for the Rust programming language The Rust Performance Book: techniques that can improve the performance—speed and memory usage—of Rust programs Dark Magic The Rustonomicon: all the awful details that you need to understand when writing Unsafe Rust programs References The Rust Reference: the primary reference for the Rust programming language Videos Considering Rust: the pros &amp; cons of Rust and how it compares with other languages Rust at speed: a real world usage example of Rust Crust of Rust: where Jon Gjengset explains one core Rust concept at a time and more good stuff on his YouTube channel Posts A THREAD ABOUT LEARNING THE RUST PROGRAMMING LANGUAGE on Twitter by Andrea Pessino Rust can be difficult to learn and frustrating, but it&rsquo;s also the most exciting thing in software development in a long time by Paul Dix Rust Tips and Tricks by Jon Gjengset Hands-On Complete all three projects in &ldquo;The Rust Programming Language&rdquo; book Exercism Rust Track: practice Rust by soling 100+ coding exercises Learn asynchronous programming and how to use Tokio by building a mini redis PNGme: An Intermediate Rust Project Talent Plan TP 201: Practical Networked Applications in Rust: A series of projects that incrementally develop a single Rust project from the ground up into a high-performance, networked, parallel and asynchronous key/value store.]]></description></item><item><title>My Favorite Quotes!</title><link>http://example.org/posts/quotes/</link><pubDate>Thu, 18 Nov 2021 22:29:04 -0500</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/quotes/</guid><description>&amp;ldquo;It is not the critic who counts: not the man who points out how the strong man stumbles or where the doer of deeds could have done better. The credit belongs to the man who is actually in the arena, whose face is marred by dust and sweat and blood, who strives valiantly, who errs and comes up short again and again, because there is no effort without error or shortcoming, but who knows the great enthusiasms, the great devotions, who spends himself in a worthy cause; who, at the best, knows, in the end, the triumph of high achievement, and who, at the worst, if he fails, at least he fails while daring greatly, so that his place shall never be with those cold and timid souls who knew neither victory nor defeat.</description></item><item><title>What Does It Mean to Be a Passionate Engineer?</title><link>http://example.org/posts/passion/</link><pubDate>Wed, 17 Nov 2021 13:03:20 -0500</pubDate><author>Author</author><guid>http://example.org/posts/passion/</guid><description><![CDATA[Let&rsquo;s Be Honest Although every engineer claims to be passionate and lifelong learners, few of them really are.
What Is Passion? What is passion? It&rsquo;s not something we only talk about during interviews or presentations. Instead, it&rsquo;s something we do, some choices we make, and some paths we take.
More specifically, it&rsquo;s about:
still searching for a better solution even when you already have a suboptimal one that works for now.]]></description></item></channel></rss>